SHWETA REDEKAR

+91 7208249661

Panvel, 410206

skredekar456@gmail.com



Performance oriented and responsive with experience in managing employee onboarding and HR records. Reliable and organized team member with the ability to communicate effectively and handle office changes. Dedicated associate with experience working in fast paced environment with diverse groups of individuals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HR Service Delivery Associate

Accenture Services Pvt Ltd | April 2022 - Oct 2022

- Solve routine problems through precedent and referral to general guidelines regarding pre- payroll
- Worked as a part of HR Operations team which is responsible for providing backend HR services to business operations through Taleo and Zendesk
- HR operations services administrative services, job analysis and employee relationship management.

Content Moderator

Accenture Services Pvt Ltd | Jan 2020 - May 2021

- Understanding client policies and guidelines and making decisions based on them
- Reviewing user reports regarding website contents

Research Analyst

Smarte Inc | June 2019 - Dec 2019

- Researching, interpreting, analyzing and presenting data related to operations, customers and other information related to the field they work
- Created and maintained database to store research data

EDUCATION

NMIMS Global Access School For Continuing Education (NGA-SCE)

MBA in Human Resource Management 2021 – 2024

Pillai College of Arts, Commerce And Science

Bachelor of Mass Media 2014 – 2017

SKILLS

- Strong organizational and timemanagement skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously
- · Experience in research and data analysis

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Digital Marketing specialist -Marketing Courses Training Academy (Oct 2018 - Dec2018)
- Certificate Course in MS Office (Sept 2018)